one week later inside the surge for doesn't fit people still missing after that deadly mudslide in Washington State
浪涌对不适合的人在华盛顿州是致命的泥石流后，仍然缺少一个星期后内
Turning Point ships finally rich free floating objects in the Indian Ocean are we closer to an answer in the mystery of flight 370
转折点终于船只在印度洋丰富的自由浮动对象是我们更接近答案在飞行370的神秘面纱
wear something California shake it by earthquake damage homes and businesses knockout power lot of mirrors long road home dogs name sassy biggest cyst from a little piece of technology
穿的东西加州动摇它由地震破坏家庭和企业的淘汰赛电源很多镜子的漫漫长路的家狗的名字从一小片技术的野蛮女友最大的囊肿
NBC News world headquarters in New York
NBC新闻全球总部设在纽约
NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt
NBC晚间新闻与莱斯特·霍尔特
good evening Moore unsettling rum balls this afternoon shattering nerves in Southern California less than a day after a 5.1 earthquake shattered Windows NT storage shelves and causing power outages
晚上好摩尔不安朗姆酒球今天下午惊天动地的神经在南加州不到5.1级地震后一天破灭的Windows NT仓储货架，造成停电
situs in Southern California say more than 100 aftershocks including a magnitude 4.1 quake this afternoon of a curtain wall damage from last night
拓扑在南加州说，超过100次余震，包​​括一个4.1级地震发生在今天下午从昨晚幕墙受损
quake was light it was powerful enough to remind and the region of what lies beneath we got more tonight from NBC's Wareham hours in Los Angeles
地震是轻是强大到足以提醒和什么谎言下，我们从NBC的韦勒姆小时在洛杉矶得到了今晚多个区域
it was a 5.1 earthquake hit list of presidents described as a very long 4 seconds
它被描述为一个很长的4秒总统的5.1级地震暗杀名单
feel like the seed starting the s*** after moving it was really scary
感觉像种子开始的S ***移动后，这是真正可怕的
100 pushups
100个俯卧撑
suede bottles and glass is broken Mr Bela's video showed a drug store clerk running for cover is a wall is good hit the floor the glass entrance of this motorcycle dealership shattered
绒面瓶和玻璃被打破贝拉先生的录像显示，一家药店店员运行盖一面墙是很好的砸在地板上这个摩托车经销店的玻璃大门震碎
Celtic the building was going to come down I've never been inside a building work out so scary
凯尔特人的建筑是要下来，我从来就不是一个建筑物内制定出这么吓人
the quakes truck at 9:09 p.m. Local just below the Whittier fault line that runs 25 miles long between Chino Hills in Whittier
在地震卡车在下午9点09分地方刚好低于运行25英里长奇诺岗在惠蒂尔之间的惠蒂尔断层线
it was centered outside La Habra near Los Angeles bar South San Diego address for North is Ventura County
它是拉哈布拉中心之外洛杉矶附近的酒吧南圣地亚哥地址是北文图拉县
customs scrabble cheat to get out
海关乱涂乱画骗出去
the quick treating a rockslide pushing boulders on to Rhodes overturning this car in Fullerton water main breaks Forest Street closures
快速治疗滑坡巨石推到罗德倾覆这款车在Fullerton水管破裂森林街封闭
2000 customers lost power
2000客户失去动力
weather in socks and the lights went out in
天气袜子和灯灭了的
camera shops in the legendary announcer this mean
在传说中的播音员相机店这意味着
is not turtley damaging Flatts at it should be taken two hearts that we can have larger
是不是turtley破坏性的Flatts它应该采取两颗心，我们可以有更大的
an expert Scotia that aftershock me continue for several days to weeks
专家斯科舍省的余震我持续数天至数周
Whitmore aftershocks this afternoon many feet are there in Fort Worth experts say there is a fart Chancey yesterday's quake of a sign of a stronger quake a head but its already say it should be a warning for people to be prepared
惠特莫尔余震今天下午很多的脚有没有在沃思堡的专家说，有屁Chancey较强地震​​的迹象，昨日的地震一个头，但它已经表示它应该是为人们准备一个警告
Lester Ram Alice tonight in Los Angeles think it rain in one week after a rain soaked hillside crash down a door quiet neighborhood in Oso Washington
莱斯特·拉姆爱丽丝今晚在洛杉矶觉得它的雨在一个星期一个雨水浸泡后的山坡上下来崩溃门安静的街区，在华盛顿奥索
beyond easy realization that some of the victims may remain in tune to the modern debris for a very long time
超越易于实现，一些受害者可能留在调谐到现代的碎片很长一段时间
moment of silence this morning at the exact moment of last Saturday's disaster a brief paws to the search operation push Crusader physical and emotional edges NBC's Miguel Almaguer remains on the scene 4s tonight and has a lake Oswego
默哀今天上午在上星期六灾难的确切时刻一个简短的爪子在搜索操作推十字军的身体和情感的边缘NBC的米格尔Almaguer仍然在现场4S今晚有奥斯威戈湖
here we saw steady rain anything but ideal conditions for search teens tonight there is real concerned over their safety as they push on
在这里，我们看到了稳定的雨什么，但对于十几岁的搜索今晚有真正关注过他们的安全，因为他们推了理想的条件
1037 a.m.
上午1037
one week to the moment a mudslide buried so much about so search teen spas to remember the victims in does the objectify
一个星期的那一刻泥石流掩埋了这么多所以搜索的青少年温泉要记住在做对象化的受害者
in small towns not far from this tight knit community heartbreak and tears
在小城镇不远处的这种紧密结合的社群心碎和眼泪
going to take a long time to heal
将需要很长的时间来愈合
290 official death toll standard 17 bodies have been found but not identified
290官方公布的死亡人数标准的17具尸体已被发现，但尚未确定
90 people are still missing
90人仍然失踪
everyday search teams make more grim discovery
每天的搜索队做出更严峻​​的发现
take Cruiser identify bodies in the field to expect your victim total to rise of the next several days
采取巡洋舰辨认尸体在现场期待你的受害者总上升在未来数天的
it's a very very slow process it was miserable to begin with n as you all know it rain last few days its me the quicksand even worse
这是一个非常非常缓慢的过程很悲惨，开始有n个大家都知道下雨过去几天了我的流沙更惨
this is what it looks like for crews on the ground a world washed away in flipped upside down search teams are exhausted suffering from hypothermia is chaplain standby
这就是它看起来像在地面人员的世界里翻转倒挂冲走搜索队枯竭患低体温是牧师待机
volunteer Salvage what they can this is all that's left
志愿者救助他们可以，这是所有剩下的
this is a very emotional affair Meridian Ford
这是一个很情绪化的事情经络福特
alongside us
我们一起
today in the rain a flash flood warning in worries all this water could trigger another slice it dangerous work it sets Jeffords knows all too well Pantera
今天在雨中的忧虑所有这些水的山洪预警可能引发另一片是危险的工作，它设置杰福兹太很好知道所有的Pantera
compass
指南针
trailer the volunteer firefighter help find his wife Christina and his granddaughter in the Robin
拖车志愿消防队员帮助寻找他的妻子克里斯蒂娜和他的孙女在罗宾
will miss my wife and daughter
会想念我的妻子和女儿
how much tonight Jeffords shares his grief with families with lost love ones and with so many others were still waiting for someone to come home
多少今晚杰福兹分享他的悲伤与家庭失去了亲人，有这么多其他人还在等待有人来家里
are we can go today 7 survivors were rescued from the mudslide tonight 50 man hospitalized AR slowly recovering
是我们能够走到今天7幸存者被从今晚泥石流50人住院治疗AR缓慢复苏抢救
Accu
电池
today for the first time in 4 weeks floating objects were recovered in the Indian Ocean net worth spected to be related to the missing Malaysian jetliner NBC's Carrie Sanders is falling down Story Forest from Washington
今天第一次在4周内浮动对象被回收spected可能与失踪客机马来西亚NBC的嘉莉·桑德斯从华盛顿落下故事森林印度洋净值
it's the first time anything is good fish from the ocean since this investigation begins is the Chinese shared news that official rather just Ocean garbage
这是第一次什么好鱼从海洋中，因为本次调查开始，是中国共享消息，而官方只是海洋垃圾
10 countries are again airborne today Chris Crossing a new patch of the Indian Ocean about the size of New Mexico
10个国家今天再次空降克里斯跨越印度洋的一个新的补丁关于新墨西哥州的大小
orange green and white items orange spotted in the last 24 hours what experts say yellow is the color to find
橙绿白橙项发现在过去24小时专家们说黄色是颜色找
looking at this to breed is expected to see anything does bright yellow weather is the emergency escape slides were the life preserver or life
看着这品种有望看到什么就亮黄色天气的紧急逃生滑梯是救生圈或生活
22 days into the political analyst a Chinese government is under extraordinary pressure
22天到政治分析家一个中国政府是在巨大的压力
how to make clear to Chinese citizens that they are doing everything conceivable to find out what
如何让清晰的中国公民，他们正在尽一切可以想象找出什么
250 family members of passengers are headed from Beijing to Kuala Lumpur weatherstrip more confusion 6 days ago
乘客的250家庭成员从北京前往吉隆坡风雨6天之前更混乱
Minister Brook Hearts 1 ounce there was no hope and 370z
部长布鲁克心1盎司没有希望和370Z
send
发送
but this today from laser that can Ministry of Transportation no matter how remote
但今天从激光器，可以交通部无论多么遥远
who is who
谁是谁
please continue to find survivors
请继续寻找幸存者
American Philip wood was on board flight 370
美国菲利普木板在船上飞行370
I'm totally confused by honestly don't understand
我完全被真的不明白混淆
why the government has behave the way it has the whole way through a heaven
为什么政府的行为有过一个天上全路的方式
tonight hi tech underwater listening devices on route to the sword so it will be told towed behind a ship to listen for the flight recorder Sphinx
今晚高科技水下监听的路线剑所以它会被告知被拖船舶后面听的飞行记录装置狮身人面像
The Spinners which are right here is supposed to send out a signal for about 30 days that means there's about 8 or 9 maybe 10 days left before the battery dies Lester I carry thank you
这是这里的纱厂应该发出一个信号，30天左右，这意味着有大约8或9，也许10天前，电池离开死亡莱斯特我背谢谢
30 Development Center in with her ports of tens of thousands of Russian troops masinger the border and their intentions not clear
30发展中心与数万俄军她口masinger边界，他们的意图尚不清楚
diplomatic efforts tonight at a surprise announcement by Secretary of State John Kerry NBC's Kristen Welker to the White House with more force
今晚突然宣布国务卿克里NBC的克里斯汀·韦尔克到白宫与更多的力量外交努力
what's a good evening secretary Kerry was headed home from Saudi Arabia today when he abruptly turned his playing around and headed to Europe to meet with his rush counterparts in Paris tomorrow this on the heels of an hour long call between President Obama
什么是一个美好的夜晚秘书克里今天头球破门来自沙特阿拉伯的时候，他突然把他玩弄，前往欧洲与他的同行抢在巴黎迎接明天这对奥巴马总统之间的一个小时长的通话高跟鞋
Russian President Putin yesterday about a possible diplomatic revolution Wallace singer in ministration official would provide details
俄罗斯总统普京昨天对可能的外交革命华莱士歌手职事官将提供详细资料
how far is heaven who did encourage in Russia police forces back to its basis and allow international monitors into Ukraine now pensions have been Mountain
多远是天堂谁在俄罗斯的警察部队并鼓励回它的基础，并允许国际观察员进入乌克兰现在养老金已经山
after Russia annexed Crimea and the mask troops near Ukraine border Russia reiterated today it has no intention of invading other parts of Ukraine
仅次于俄罗斯吞并克里米亚和掩码部队附近乌克兰边境今日俄罗斯重申，它无意侵略乌克兰其他地区
the White House says it has to wait and see how serious is about diplomacy
白宫表示，它已经以观望严重的是关于外交如何
so far he's been defiant Lester
到目前为止，他一直反抗莱斯特
alright Christian thanks just one week before the presidential election in Afghanistan Taliban militants carita big attack in Kabul today this for this week Archie foreign correspondent Richard Engel is there tonight
短短一个星期，阿富汗塔利班武装分子在总统选举之前正常的基督徒感谢在喀布尔凯伊黛大发作今天这个这个星期阿奇外国记者理查德·恩格尔是今晚有
grieving Lester all indications are there going to be a very violent election in fact it already is
悲伤的莱斯特所有的迹象都存在将是一个非常暴力的选举实际上它已经是
today the headquarters of reactants Electoral Commission was attacked the word dozens of election officials inside
今天的反应物选举委员会的总部遭到袭击的数十字内的选举官员
when suddenly started receiving incoming rocketfire gunfire rush down into safe room for several hours eventually Afghan security forces mother to set up a Courtin around the area moving
当突然开始接收传入rocketfire炮火赶下来到安全的房间了几个小时，最终阿富汗安全部队的母亲设立一个COURTIN周围地区移动
who won the building 700 yards away from me
谁赢得了大厦700码距离我
quarters were born to live on military and pick it up position clear the building and killed before Taliban militants in some ways dissizit indication of the United States is leaving behind the Afghan security forces today didn't succeed
宿舍出生住在军事和把它捡起来定位明确的建设和塔利班武装分子在某些DISSIZIT美国的指示留下阿富汗安全部队今天没有成功的方式杀死前
the Taliban is increasingly bold increasingly carry out more frequent attacks right here in the Afghan capital letter
塔利班是越来越大胆越来越多地进行更频繁的攻击，在这里，在阿富汗首都信
Richard Engel in Cabo more damage control today from New Jersey Governor Chris Christie who spoke today in Las Vegas today after again trying to put the George Washington Bridge scandal behind him today is pokerus on leadership
理查德·恩格尔在擦玻璃更从今天新泽西州州长克里斯·克里斯蒂今天谁在拉斯维加斯后，今天再次尝试今天把乔治·华盛顿大桥丑​​闻在他身后说话损坏控制pokerus上领导
how do you get better
你如何获得更好的
how do you make your people better
你如何让你更好的人
it's so for me I think its about
它是如此对我来说，我认为其对
me peeing a lot more questioning
我嘘嘘了很多质疑
about things are going on
事情是怎么回事
it's about sending very clear signal for certain contacts and actions are acceptable in certain are completely all except
它是关于某些联系人和行动派遣非常明确的信号是可以接受在某些完全以外的所有
our political director Chuck Todd is falling all this tonight Chuck
我们的政治部主任查托德正在下降这一切今晚查
Wallace Richmond fascinated watch crystal the last 4 days let's put into contacts wear Christie was today in Las Vegas this was a 2016 Republican cattle call
华莱士里士满着迷手表晶体的持续4天，让我们投入触点磨损今天克里斯蒂是在拉斯维加斯，这是2016年共和党牛呼叫
if you want to call about a bunch of potential 2016 presidential candidates were there
如果你想打电话讲了一堆潜在的2016总统候选人在那里
so let's look at this remarkable 72 hours
所以让我们来看看这个了不起的72小时
chris Christie comes out with his own investigation at Claire's Hymn of wrongdoing
克里斯·克里斯蒂出来与他自己的调查在不道德的行为克莱尔的歌
does a network television interview does it matter press conference for the bravado comes back it starts attacking reporters trying to basic lease a you don't know what you're talking about again
没有一个网络电视采访有什么关系新闻发布会，虚张声势回来它开始攻击记者试图基本租赁一你不知道你在说什么再
quickly get on a plane does he wants to jump start his presidential campaign still wants to run for president and that's the biggest out of this political purgatory
赶紧上飞机就他想跳开始他的总统竞选仍想竞选总统，这就是最大的了这种政治炼狱
but as we saw today we had some new photos released
但正如我们今天看到的，我们有一些新的照片发布
that came out the September 11 commemoration I was taking place down near Ground Zero and look who is whipped
说出来的9月11日纪念我正在发生向下世贸遗址附近，看看谁是鞭打
all of the key players is on September 11 2013 is with all of the key players from the New Jersey Port Authority in left for all those guy Samson while sitting perroni
所有的关键球员是在2013年9月11日与所有从新泽西港务局留下的关键球员为所有那些家伙参孙而坐perroni
all of them with the governor wild the bread while the bridge tire plus happening in real time and again of course
所有的人都与州长野面包，而课程的桥梁轮胎加上发生在现实一次又一次
it's been a case of sweet 6s for candy crush to Wylie popular video game has been captivating tens of millions of an infant first came out a couple of years ago in this week the company that makes it went public NBC's erica Hill has more the crazy over candy crush
它一直甜6S糖果美眉卫理流行的视频游戏已经被迷人的数以千万计的婴儿的情况下首先来到了一个几年前在本周的公司，使得它去公共N​​BC的埃里卡山有更疯狂的了糖果美眉
the game the taking over smartphones and tablets everywhere
游戏中的接管智能手机和平板电脑无处不在
candy crush saga sugar is sweet lord
糖果美眉传奇糖是甜的领主
user scream and rows of colorful candy crush level 100 million game being played every day you took the price candy crush has inspired treat candy bar in New York along with socks
用户尖叫和行丰富多彩的糖果压榨一级亿正在玩的游戏的每一天，你拿着糖果价格美眉启发在纽约享受的直板连同袜子
jewelry phone cases they didn't see this coming
饰品手机情况下，他们并没有看到这一切
we knew that we had a good core concept on our hands but the popularity within itself
我们知道我们有一个很好的核心理念在我们的手中，但在本身的普及
Alex Kingston whited ages 25 255 are the game the most loyal customers
亚历克斯金士顿粉饰的年龄在25255顷游戏中最忠实的客户
can't believe just how hot big book come eat in celebrity now united in the quest to conquer the cross
不能相信是多么热的大书来吃饭的名人现在统一在追求征服交叉
can you pass level strap Minot with root together
你可以通过一级带迈诺特与根一起
trouble trouble
烦
play the game of the quiet place to do it is the secret room
玩安静的地方做的游戏是密室
Tech decks birthdate of people who wouldn't normally consider themselves gamers easy to get into
谁的人通常不会认为自己是游戏玩家很容易进入高科技甲板生日
SRQ very slowly rewards novice players make him feel like they're cheating some things I can keep going
SRQ非常缓慢奖励新手玩家让他觉得像他们欺骗一些事情，我可以坚持下去
interior designer Jane mogul begin playing when she needed a little break
室内设计师简巨头开始玩的时候，她需要稍微休息一下
how does it help you decompress I find a very relaxing and its opposite from my work
它是如何帮助你解我发现一个非常轻松和它的对立面从我的工作
for more than an hour a day Austin when she's supposed to be spending time with her husband Peter Pitts
一个多小时，每天奥斯汀，当她应该是花时间与她的丈夫彼得·皮茨
together to feel a little bit of your wife
一起去感受你的妻子一点点
download free users can move along work with Lisa buy extra lives for 99 cents which can it up
下载免费用户可以沿着移动的工作与丽莎购买额外的生命为99美分，可它
James and not ready to log off of good times 2
詹姆斯和不准备注销的美好时光2
level 50 in on slimming for a long time to hang a parakeet Hill NBC News New York
对减肥很长一段时间挂一只长尾鹦鹉山NBC新闻纽约50级
and we're back of America homecoming a long way to finally over
而我们又回到美国归国的很长的路终于结束了
asthma attack news today's a lesson tonight and a Happy New Year in a half a dog names that wander way was reunited with owner last night the result of a chance encounter with a vet us the right questions we got a story to die from NBC still Rapaport
哮喘发作的消息，今天是一个教训，今晚和新年快乐的一半，顺便逛逛一只狗的名字团聚与业主昨晚与兽医偶然相遇的结果我们我们得到了一个故事，从美国全国广播公司死亡的权利的问题仍然拉帕波特
when you think that there is no help at all
当你认为有没有帮助
the really and truly is hope
的的确确是希望
you never give up its been an egg in icing 17 months for Cindy Romans since her beloved beagles 7 year old sassy who she raised
你永远不会放弃其一直是在结冰1​​7个月为辛迪罗鸡蛋，因为她心爱的小猎犬7岁的时髦，她提出了谁
the puppy wonder doll from a family members home and never returned we drive up and down the road looking to see if possibly should been hit by car nothing
从一个家庭成员的小狗奇迹娃娃家，再也没有回来，我们开车上下的道路寻找，看看是否有可能要被击中的车什么
you just come to come to terms with the fact that she's she's gone but sassy did survive for studying death from a severe injury sensuous into a kill shelter by state had other plans for this lucky hound
你只是来达成协议的事实，她是她已经走了，但时髦却存活研究死亡一重伤感性到杀住所由国家却另有打算为这个幸运的猎犬
sassy travel from rush Kentucky to Ashland to Huntington West Virginia and eventually to Brentwood Pennsylvania covering more than 400 miles to find rolling into a foster home
时髦从急于前往肯塔基州阿什兰亨廷顿西弗吉尼亚州，并最终以宾夕法尼亚州布伦特伍德覆盖超过400公里 - 找到擀成一个寄养家庭
is all is your pet in her and giving her attention gsapp a very low maintenance
所有被您的宠物在她和给她的注意力GSAPP一个非常低的维护
but it last week best visit a revelation
但上周最佳浏览启示
they said she microchipped and turns out that she was before that we were calling her jenni as soon as they said she's microchip in her name is sassy diva tell right away she react that
他们说，她和植入芯片原来，她在此之前，我们只要他们说，她的微芯片在她的名字叫她JENNI是时髦的女歌手告诉马上反应过来，她那
microchip with the missing piece to sassy past Barracuda animal
微芯片与失踪一块时髦的过去酷鱼动物
every year of being reunited with their owners because of that microchip
每年的团聚，因为微芯片与它们的主人
it's a small device about the size of a grain of rice in planted in the animals scanners detect a chip in link to tattoo a database that links back to their owners sassy this was a reunion the Romans have prayed for
它是关于大米的粮食种植在动物扫描仪检测到一个芯片中的链接以纹身，链接回他们的所有者时髦，这是一个团圆的罗马人祈求一个数据库的大小的小型设备
BBC News
BBC新闻
MSNBC nightly news for this Saturday I'm Lester Holt reporting from your coffee tomorrow morning on today in right back here tomorrow evening have a great night
这个星期六MSNBC的晚间新闻，我莱斯特霍尔特从你的咖啡明早今天在右后卫位置明晚报告有一个伟大的夜晚